j-stay.jp 2019-05-30

# Privacy Policy of J-Stay

This website (http://www.j-stay.jp/) is operated and managed by J-Hoppers Co., Ltd. (hereinafter referred to as “the Company”). Before using this website, please read and agree to the following terms. It is assumed that the person using this website (hereinafter refer to as “the user”) has agreed to these terms before use.

### 1\. Information Collection and Use

J-Stay collects various personal information including your name, age, gender, occupation, nationality, phone number, e-mail address, and type of visa. This personal information is used only for further communication between you and J-Stay, for the sole purpose of renting a room. Also when confriming a reservation, we may require credit card details instead of a direct desposit. Your personal information will be put into our database for management, and your credit card informaiton will be erased when you sign a lease contract or if a cancellation of a reservation is made. The information will not be used for any other purpose, nor will it be provided to other groups or parties. You have the right to change/delete/request a copy of the information which we hold about you.

### _2\. Cookies_

When you visit our website, like most other websites we send one or more cookies--small anonymous identifiers--to your computer that uniquely identify your browser. While we do use cookies for security and fraud investigation purposes, our primary purpose is to enhance your user experience by understanding and remembering your preferences, and by the general tracking of our user trends. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or to notify you when a cookie is sent. Please be aware that some of our features and services may not have full functionality if your browser refuses cookies.

### _3\. Links_

Sites that are linked to ours may have different policies; please review the privacy policy notices on those sites for more details.

### _4\. Changes to this Privacy Policy_

We may update or modify this privacy policy from time to time in the future. Any such updates or modifications shall be effective immediately upon their posting. Please refer back to this page often for the latest information.

### _5\. Questions and Suggestions_

If you have any questions or concerns about this Policy, you may e-mail or contact us by phone.   
J-Hoppers Co., Ltd. [Address: 229, Kogawa-cho, Shimogyo-ku, Kyoto-shi, Kyoto] [Tel : 075-634-4944]

## Disclaimer

### 1\. Liability

Every effort is made to keep the website up and running smoothly. However, J-Stay takes no responsibility for, and will not be liable for, the website being temporarily unavailable due to technical issues beyond our control.

### _2\. External Links_

The website may provide links to other internet sites for the convenience of our users. J-Stay is not responsible for the availability or content of these external sites, nor does J-Stay endorse, warrant, or guarantee the products, services, or information described or offered at the sites in question. It is the responsibility of the user to examine the copyright and licensing restrictions of linked pages and to secure all necessary permissions.

### _3\. Room Availability  _

Room availability shown on each property is not real-time. The data is renewed as soon as there is a change in availability, however it may not reflect the actual availability.

### _4\. Room Condition_

Photographs and videos of our rooms are taken when the premises were vacant. Therefore, actual condition of the rooms (ex. color of the curtains or types of furniture) may differ. If you would like to know the specific condition of a room, please contact us.
